<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Anthony Liao</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Anthony Liao</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automated Irrigation Project with IoT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/auto-irrigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/auto-irrigation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While working on the Field and Fork Farms, I wanted to use my technical background to create a system that would make tasks on the farms easier, one of them being managing irrigation. Currently on the farm, irrigation is semi-manual, by setting timers in person on the farm that controls a schedule for the irrigation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/files/FinalReportAnthonyLiao.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Read our project proposal here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The premise of this project is to use capacitive soil moisture sensors to determine when it is best to water the fields. Using measures of moisture, temperature, and light, we want to use this data to turn on and off a solenoid valve, and send all this data to an online dashboard where data can be monitored and valves can be controlled. With remote irrigation, no one needs to be on the farm to monitor the irrigation, and no one will have to manually turn it off during times of heavy rain or wet periods.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecological Niche Modeling for Responses to Climate Change</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/cure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/cure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project I worked on for a class in the spring of 2024. I worked with Dr. Pamela Soltis, Dr. Douglas Soltis, and Dr. Makenzie Mabry, who work at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.floridamuseum.ufl.edu/soltis-lab/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Soltis Lab&lt;/a&gt;. The goal of the project was to model what will happen to Florida plant communities and ecosystems as a response to climate change using niche modeling and the UF supercomputer cluster HiPerGator.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/files/FinalReportAnthonyLiao.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Read my final report here!&lt;/a&gt;Or keep reading for a more brief summary. My poster is at the bottom of this page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field and Fork Farm Gardens Internship</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/fieldfork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/fieldfork/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://fieldandfork.ufl.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Learn more about Field and Fork&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I started volunteering here in 2023 after I found out that UF has a sustainable agriculture farm. The Field and Fork Farm is connected to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://pantry.fieldandfork.ufl.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hitchcock Pantry&lt;/a&gt;, and provides fresh and organic produce for people at UF experiencing food insecurity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/FF/compost.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been working as an intern here, managing the Composting and The International Forest Gardens, along with doing other regular tasks such as harvesting, planting, and weeding. Working here, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot of skills and gained a lot of experience that I would have never had otherwise, or gotten the chance to pick up. I feel very lucky to have worked here!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Intelligence Lab</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/mil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/mil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mil.ufl.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Machine Intelligence Lab&lt;/a&gt; is a UF research lab that focuses on development of intelligent, autonomous robots. While I worked here, we focused primarily on two competitions- &lt;a href=&#34;https://robosub.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RoboSub&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://robotx.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RobotX&lt;/a&gt;. We worked mainly on two autonomous robots:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;button onclick=&#34;window.open(&#39;https://subjugator.org/&#39;, &#39;_blank&#39;);&#34; &#xA;style=&#34;margin-left: 250px; padding: 10px 20px; background-color: #007bff; color: white; border: none; border-radius: 5px; cursor: pointer;&#34;&gt;&#xA;SubjuGator&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/MIL/sub8.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;button onclick=&#34;window.open(&#39;https://navigatoruf.org/&#39;, &#39;_blank&#39;);&#34; &#xA;style=&#34;margin-left: 250px; padding: 10px 20px; background-color: #007bff; color: white; border: none; border-radius: 5px; cursor: pointer;&#34;&gt;&#xA;NaviGator&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
